<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Permaculture</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Permaculture</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About Welcome to my permaculture blog! I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share my knowledge and experiences in permaculture design with you.
Who Am I? I&amp;rsquo;m a dedicated permaculture enthusiast residing in the beautiful South-West of England. Armed with a permaculture design certificate, I am deeply passionate about sustainable living, natural building techniques, and creating vibrant food forests.
What is Permaculture? Permaculture is an innovative approach to designing and creating sustainable, regenerative systems that mimic nature&amp;rsquo;s patterns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Guide to Permaculture: Designing Sustainable Ecosystems</title>
      <link>/posts/permaculture-designing-sustainable-ecosystems.2023-06-12t11-46-34.103z/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/permaculture-designing-sustainable-ecosystems.2023-06-12t11-46-34.103z/</guid>
      <description>Permaculture is a holistic approach to designing sustainable ecosystems that are self-sufficient and require little maintenance. It is based on the principles of earth care, people care, and fair share. The goal of permaculture is to create a system where everything works together in harmony - from the smallest microorganisms in the soil to the largest trees in the forest.
In today&amp;rsquo;s world, where climate change and environmental degradation are major concerns, permaculture offers an alternative way of living that is kinder to our planet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
